https://www.rejuvenation-science.com/aboutus/privacy-policy

HomeProductsONLINE STORE
Complete Product List Products by Category Product Search
A Immune SupportAdvanced Diet a...Anti-Aging & Fu...AntioxidantAppetite ControlBasic HealthBone HealthBooksBrain and MemoryBrandsCBD HempCoQ10Diet and Weight...DigestionHair CareHeart HealthHormone SupportInflammationIntestinal Heal...Joint HealthLifespanLiver HealthMen's HealthMetabolic EnergyMineralsMinor Pain Mana...New ProductsOmega-3Overall HealthPediatric HealthPromosRadiation Prote...Respiratory HealthSkin CareSleepSpecialsSports & FitnessStress and Rela...Syndrome XVegetarianVisionVitaminsWomen's Health
Research/NewsFAQ’sAbout UsContact UsAbout UsTerms of UseTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyTopics Advanced Cartilage Support™Anti-AgingBasic HealthBiom3ga™ Krill OilBredesen ProtocolCardiovascular HealthCBD HempCBD Hemp Doctor FAQsCBD, THC, and the Endocannabinoid System – A PrimerCellular EnergyCoenzyme Q10 - UbiquinolCognitive HealthCushion Joints with Hyaluronic AcidGreen TeaHomocysteine as Risk FactorImmune SupportInflammationIntestinal Health - Probiotics and FOSJoint HealthLifespanLubricate Joints with Cetyl MyristoleateMaximum Vitality® MultivitaminMetabolic EnergyMicro-Contaminant DetoxOmega-3 Fish OilPractitioner Multivitamin ComparisonQualitySkeletal Calcium™SleepTax DeductibilityVisionWeight LossCellular Optimizer Results
Privacy Policy
Print
At Rejuvenation Science we protect your privacy as if it were our own. We use the information you provide to us for five purposes only: to process your order(s), to reply to your questions, provide our newsletter via email and to incorporate your feedback into improvements to our Web site, and to report transactional, but not personal information, to your doctor. We will not give, sell, or rent your personal information or specific account activity to anyone for any reason except as required by law. Our Secure Ordering:At Rejuvenation Science we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt the information you send us when you place your order. The information is encrypted on your computer, sent through the Internet as jumbled code, and decoded on Rejuvenation Science's secure server. It cannot be read in transit. Credit Card Fraud Protection:All major credit card companies protect cardholders against fraud, subject to a $50 deductible. Rejuvenation Science will protect you for this $50 portion in the highly unlikely situation that you ever encounter an inappropriate charge involving our company. Optional Fax Ordering:If you are still skeptical about placing your order online, you may place your order via fax at 310-798-2830 at any time, day or night. Information We Collect: In designing our website, we started with the simple belief that customer service is our number one priority. Therefore the customer information we collect is used to enhance our services to our customers. When you visit our website, we collect information about your visit:We collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, and we log the length of time of your visit and the number of times you visit and purchase from us. We assign you a unique internal identifier to help keep track of your future visits. We use this information to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors, and we may use it to personalize the information you see on our website and the emails you receive from us (should you grant us permission to send to you). We keep this information for our internal use; we do not share it with others. Our site uses cookies to store information between visits to our site:Cookies are a mechanism to remember information about a visitor from one page to another. Web browsers store cookies so that the browser itself can remember some information and then, on request, pass all that information up to the server at one time. We use cookies to remember your name and the contents of your shopping cart. This allows you to leave our site, come back later, and still have the contents of your shopping cart intact. It also lets us personalize your experience at Rejuvenation Science, tailoring the content to your interests. Our website requires the use of cookies. Turning off cookies or rejecting the Rejuvenation Science cookie will prevent you from accessing the website. When you subscribe to our newsletter, Rejuvenation Science, asks you for contact information (your name and email address). When you sign up for our newsletter we use your name and email address to send you our health newsletter and to inform you of sales and special offers.
Recommend product or information to a friend:The information collected is used to send an email to the friend letting them know about the product that the user recommends or the scientific information for your friend to read. A follow-up e-mail may be sent to your friend. If you place an online order, our secure order form requests contact, billing, and financial information (such as your credit card numbers for purchases). Contact information from the order form (email address, name, billing and shipping address, and phone number) is used to send orders and information about our company to you. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you should we have questions regarding your order or should we need to notify you of the status of your order. And yes, you can opt not to get email from us, as described in the opt-out section below. The financial information we collect is used ONLY to bill you for products you purchase. For your convenience, your information including credit card and order history may be stored on a secure server that allows you to reorder by entering your email address and password. This information is not shared with any outside parties unless you came to the site from an affiliate site. See the affiliate section below. You may also place an autoship order that will allow you to receive products on a regular basis without the need to reenter that order every time. You may cancel this order at anytime by sending an email to
sales (at) rejuvenation-science (dot) com. You will automatically be registered to receive our newsletter unless you opt-out at the time of purchase. You may opt-out at any later time by following the unsubscribe instructions in the newsletter or sending an email to info (at) rejuvenation-science (dot) com. We have several types of third-party relationships:
We have an affiliate program that allows your doctor and other websites to earn money by directing people (through links) to our website. If you sign up as an affiliate, your contact information (website address and related information, email address, mailing and payment addresses, and contact information) is kept in-house. No third parties are used.
We use third-party intermediaries. When you purchase from us, we send your credit card information, name, and billing address to credit card companies for verification and to authorize your purchase.
Our affiliates may have access to transaction-level data:Our affiliate program offers a feature that allows your referring doctor or a small number of selected affiliates to gain access to individual user transaction information that originates from links on their websites. These affiliates generally include, but are not limited to, member sites, charity fund-raising sites, school fund-raising sites, and association sites. To properly track and credit the customer's transaction, these sites may give each of their members a unique code, which will uniquely identify the member or the member's organization. This code is activated only when the customer links directly from the affiliate site to Rejuvenation Science or uses their doctor discount code. Any transactions made at Rejuvenation Science while the code is active will be reported back to the affiliate. Rejuvenation Science never passes on personal data as part of this feature. We will provide only the date of the transaction, the amount of the transaction, and the product purchased. To further protect the privacy of our customers, we require all affiliates requesting this feature to sign a statement promising to inform users beforehand of any such data collection, and to guarantee that any data collected will be used solely to reward users (or their selected charities) for their purchases. If you are concerned about having your purchase tracked in this manner, you may avoid it by visiting Rejuvenation Science directly (without linking from an affiliate site). If the affiliate site has not made its tracking procedures clear to you, please notify us by e-mail at
info (at) rejuvenation-science (dot) com. We occasionally run our own online surveys and we ask visitors for contact information (such as email address) and demographic information (such as zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send users information about our company. You may opt-out of the survey and also opt-out of any future mailings at the time of the survey. The demographic information is used to learn more about the types of people who visit our site. This information is not shared with any other parties currently. We reserve the right to share this information with other parties in the future in an aggregated format that would not disclose any personally identifiable information. We may run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their email address). We use this information to contact the winners and to send visitors information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings at the time they enter the contest; see the opt-out section below. Opt-Out:If you decide to opt out of our newsletter, our emails provide you the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us. You can also opt-out by sending an email to
info (at) rejuvenation-science (dot) com with the word unsubscribe followed by your email address in the subject line of the email. Links:This site contains links to other sites. Rejuvenation Science is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites. Delete/Deactivate:This site gives you the following options to not receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service.
You can send email to
info (at) rejuvenation-science (dot) com You can send mail to the following postal address:
Rejuvenation Science, Inc. 5334 Torrance Blvd., 2nd FloorTorrance, CA 90503
Change/ModifyOur site provides you the opportunity to correct or update your account information. You can do this by:
Send us an email note to info (at) rejuvenation-science (dot) com Send mail to the following postal address:
Rejuvenation Science, Inc.5334 Torrance Blvd., 2nd FloorTorrance, CA 90503
When You Send Email to our Customer Service Department:We provide email links on our site that allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. The information you send us is used to respond directly to your questions and comments. We also keep your email correspondence on file so that we may better serve you should you have additional questions in the future. Your personal information is shared with third parties (such as manufacturers) only with your explicit permission. How We Notify You of Changes to our Privacy Policy:Whenever we change our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our website indicating that a new version is available. If Rejuvenation Science changes how it uses a users personally identifiable information, the user will be notified by email and they may opt-out at that time. However, if you have opted-out of all communication with the site you will not be contacted, nor will your personally identifiable information be used in this new manner. Contacting the Web Site:If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: Customer ServiceRejuvenation Science5334 Torrance Blvd., 2nd FloorTorrance, CA 90503Fax:(310) 798-2830email:
info (at) rejuvenation-science (dot) com
NEW PRODUCTS
Superfoods Immune Energizer
Featured Research/News
Omega-3 Fatty Acids Equal or More Effective than NSAIDs
Migraines Associated With Increased Heart Attack Risk:
Mitochondria Function Implicated in Both
Calcium Supplementation
More Effective Than Sodium Reduction in Lowering Blood Pressure
